A Guide to the Records of the Virginia State Board of Elections, Campaign Finance Division, Campaign Expense Accounts, 1992-2007
Library of Virginia
- II. Virginia House of Delegates, 1993-2005., Extent: 6 cubic feet (6 boxes). (Box 22-25, 29-30)
  - Rapp, Melanie - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Raynol, Timothy - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Reese, Gary - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Reid, Jack - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Reynolds, Kimble - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Rinker, Jim - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Robinson, William - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Rogers, Douglas - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Rollinson, John - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Rowe, Michael - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Sass, Stephen - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Sears, Winsome - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Sheffield, Eric - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Shepard, Brian - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Strong, Al - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Stump, Jackie - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Suit, Terrie - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Thomas, Victor - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Thomapson, Walton - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Tobar, Andres - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Tuck, Donnie - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Van Yahres, Mitchell - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Wagner, Yvonne - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Ward, Forrest - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Welch, John - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Wike, Bradley - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Williams, Lois - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Williams, Robert - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Wolfe, Bonnie - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Wyatt, Linda - 2003 (Box 25)
  - Albo, David - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Ball, Michael - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Barg, Hilda - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Beals, Thomas - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Bratsnhi, Michael - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Burchard, Albert - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Casey, David - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Coggeshall, John - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Danner, Christopher - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Davis, Radley - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Delvin, Sean - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Dpkrepaulezz, Diallo - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Eby, Charles - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Elder, Bruce - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Enos-Edu, James - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Ferguson, Donald - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Ferguson, Eric - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Flowers, Jerry - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Garber, Robert - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Garvey, Elizabeth - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Gilliland, Randall - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Glenn, Gerald - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Goodall, Shirley - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Goodwyn, Deborah - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Gregerson, Christopher - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Grignol, Ronald - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Harvey, Shirley - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Haugh, Daniel - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Herron, Richard - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Hobson, Richard - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Hyland, James - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Jarvis, Robert - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Kenney, Shaun - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Kern, Donnie - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Koleszar, Stephen - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Law, Melvin - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Lay, James - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Levy, Levi - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Lee, Deborah - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Marrs, Bradley - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Mason, John - 2005 (Box 29)
  - McCarty, Rex - 2005 (Box 29)
  - McEachin, Donald - 2005 (Box 29)
  - McPherson, Brian - 2005 (Box 29)
  - Miles, Delceno - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Mueda, Matthew - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Nicolson, John - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Oleszek, Janet - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Palmiotto, Mario - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Parmele, John - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Purves, Arthur - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Saunders, Carson - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Schmidt, Peter - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Sims, Andrea - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Skeeter, Walter - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Tingley, Clement - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Tribbett, Benjamin - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Volpe, Marianne - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Werkheiser, Gregory - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Williams, Anthony - 2005 (Box 30)
  - Young, David (Box 30)
- III. Virginia State Senate, 1992-2003., Extent: 2 cubic feet (2 boxes). (Box 26-27)
  - Maxwell, W. Henry - 1992 (Box 26)
  - Coleman, Barbara J. - 1995 (Box 26)
  - Parris, Stanford - 1995 (Box 27)
  - Quayle, M. Frederick - 1995 (Box 26)
  - Couric, Emily - 1999 (Box 26)
  - Maxwell, W. Henry - 1999 (Box 26)
  - Deeds, Creigh - 2001 (Box 26)
  - Jones, Sharon L. - 2001 (Box 26)
  - Belter, Cathy - 2002 (Box 26)
  - Cuccinelli, Kenneth - 2002 (Box 26)
  - O'Brien, Jay - 2002 (Box 26)
  - Askew, Verbena - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Berrios, Daniel - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Blevins, Harry - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Bomersheim, Phillip - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Braunlich, Christian - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Brown, Walter - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Christian, Ron - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Church, Joseph - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Clarke, Robert - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Delvolites, Jeannemarie - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Eagle, Rodney - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Emick, Stephen - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Gallgan, Gregory - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Gonzalez, Richard - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Graves, James - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Graziano, Joseph - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Green, Donald - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Griffin, II, Stone Phillip - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Harrison, Erenestine - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Hawkins, Charles - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Herbert, William - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Herring, Mark - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Hobson, Joyce - 2003 (Box 26)
  - Holland, Clarence - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Holtzman, William - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Hunt, Dave - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Jackson, Tim - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Johnson, Brenda - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Jost, Paul - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Levy, Charles - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Lind, Howie - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Lynch, Rosemary - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Maddux, Jane - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Mceachin, A. Donald - 2003 (Box 27)
  - McIntyre, James - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Minor, Mary - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Mitchell, James - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Nawash, Kamal - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Newman, Stephen - 2003 (Box 27)
  - O'Brien, James - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Protogyrou, Andrew - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Reed, Becky - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Rinker, James - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Rothfield, Michael - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Sheffield, Anthony - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Sisson, Steven - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Stankewick, Walter - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Tate, Mark - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Tederick, Matthew - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Trumbo, Malfound - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Wall, Linda - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Wilkinson, Dale - 2003 (Box 27)
  - Williams, E. Martin - 2003 (Box 27)
- IV. Statewide, 2001 and 2005., Extent: 1 cubic feet (1 boxes). (Box 28)
  Series is arranged chronologically. The Statewide series contains campaign finance reports for candidates for Governor, Lt. Governor and Attorney General
  - Diamonstein, Alan - 2001 (Box 28)
  - Forbes, Randy - 2001 (Box 28)
  - Jones, Jerrauld - 2001 (Box 28)
  - McEachin, Donald - 2001 (Box 28)
  - Kaine, Timothy - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Fitch, George - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Hudgins, William - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Kilgore, Jerry - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Baskerville, Viola - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Bolling, William - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Byrne, Leslie - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Connaughton, Sean - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Davis, Gilbert - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Hanger, Emmett - 2005 (Box 28)
  - May, Joseph - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Petersen, John - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Pucket, Phillip - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Edwards, John - 2005 (Box 28)
  - Pandak, Sharon - 2005 (Box 28)